University of Connecticut, College of Continuing Studies Records 1998.0295
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
University of Connecticut, College of Continuing Studies Records
1930s-1990s
1998.0295
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
20.0 Linear feet
The collection contains documentation of programs and activities managed, coordinated or sponsored by the office now known as the Center for Continuing Studies at the University of Connecticut. The Center was identified previously as the College of Continuing Studies or coordinated the University's Non-Degree, Summer, Intersession and Extension Programs.
History
The University of Connecticut’s Center for Continuing Studies (CCS) extends the intellectual capital and academic resources of New England’s top-ranked public university throughout the state and beyond. In collaboration with the University community, the Center designs, plans, and manages credit and non-credit educational and outreach programs appropriate to the University’s land grant mission of fostering engaged scholarship.
website
Access
The collection is open and available for research with the exception of the contents of Series I and II.
Scope and Contents
The collection contains documentation of programs and activities managed, coordinated or sponsored by the office now known as the Center for Continuing Studies at the University of Connecticut. The Center was identified previously as the College of Continuing Studies or coordinated the University's Non-Degree, Summer, Intersession and Extension Programs.
Provenance and Acquisition
The materials have been transferred periodically to the University Archives by the Center.
Related Material
Archives & Special Collections has a substantial collection of materials pertaining to the University, its history, administration, faculty, staff and students, etc.]. For detailed information on these collections please contact the curator or ask at the Reading Room desk.
University of Connecticut; Administrative Records.; Archives.; Financial Records.; Fliers. [printed matter]; Manuscripts.; Publications.; University of Connecticut.
- Series I: Non-Credit Program Records, 1947-1978
  Access
  The contents of Series I are restricted.
  - 1947-1963 (Box 1)
    Scope and Contents note
    Administrative and Financial Records, Transcript, Manuscript [Subjects include: Conferences, Class Listings, Rosters, Curriculums, Mental Health and Risk Management Reliability.]
  - 1964-1966 (Box 2)
    Administrative and Financial Records, Notes, Transcript and manuscript, Publication [Subjects include: Course Listings.]
  - 1967-1968 (Box 3)
    Administrative and Financial Records, Transcripts, Manuscripts [Subjects include: Conference Listings.]
  - 1968-1970 (Box 4)
    Administrative and Financial Records, Transcripts, Notes, Manuscripts [Subjects include: Conference Listings.]
  - 1970-1972 (Box 5)
    Administrative and Financial Records, Transcripts, Notes, Manuscripts [Subjects include: Conference and Class Listings.]
  - 1972-1974 (Box 6)
    Administrative and Financial Records, Transcripts, Notes, Manuscripts, Fliers [Subjects include: Conference Listings.]
  - 1951-1975 (Box 7)
    Correspondence, Transcript, Administrative Records [Subjects include: Annual Reports.]
  - 1950-1978 (Box 8)
    Administrative Records, Fliers, Manuscripts, Publications [Subjects include: Quality Control Rosters, Sample Conference Brochures.]
- Series II: Bachelor of General Studies Program, undated
  - A - F, undated (Box 2006-0236_1)
  - G - N, undated (Box 2006-0236_2)
  - O - Z, undated (Box 2006-0236_3)
- Series III: Publications, 1937-1983
  - Publications and brochures, 1937-1983 (Box 2009-0109_1)
  - Publications and brochures, 1937-1983 (Box 2009-0109_2)
  - Publications and brochures, 1937-1983 (Box 2009-0109_3)
- Series IV: Labor Education Center, 1962-2006
  - Annual reports, 1970-2006 (Box 2011-0099_1)
  - Annual reports, 1962-1966 (Box 2011-0099_2)
- Series V: Program files, undated
  - Global Executive Summit, undated (Box 9)
  - Homeland Security, undated (Box 9)
- Series VI: Bachelor of General Studies Photographs, Early 1980s, 1987-1988, 1993-1998, 2000-2005; 4.2 Linear feet 22.4 linear feet in total; takes up 4.2 linear feet of shelf space
  - Correspondence, fliers, notes, optical disk, 2001-2002; 1.4 Linear feet As received (Box 2012.0071_1)
    Scope and Content Note
    Subjects include: Christine Hurst.
  - Fliers, notes, optical disks, photographs, 2002; 1.4 Linear feet As received (Box 2012.0071_2)
    Subjects include: Michael Bradford, testimonial ads.
  - Administrative records, correspondence, photographs, 1997; 1.4 Linear feet As received (Box 2012.0071_3)
    Subjects include: commencement photographs taken by Caren Dickman.
  - Clippings, fliers, optical disk, photographs, 1995-1996; 1.4 Linear feet As received (Box 2012.0071_4)
    Subjects include: Denise Kalkstein, John Bishop, testimonial ads.
  - Correspondence, fliers, optical disk, photographs, 1995-1997; 1.4 Linear feet As received (Box 2012.0071_5)
    Subjects include: Barry D'Onofrio, Denise Merrill, Shellie Peck, testimonial ads.
  - Clippings, correspondence, fliers, magnetic disks, notes, optical disk, photographs, 1994; 1.4 Linear feet As received (Box 2012.0071_6)
    Subjects include: The Chronicle (Willimantic, CT), Edward Carroll, Mary Yale, testimonial ads, University of Connecticut Health Center.
  - Clippings, notes, photographs, 1987; 1.4 Linear feet As received (Box 2012.0071_7)
    Subjects include: Adam Morocco, Arline Piccolo, Carolyn Berger, The Chronicle (Willimantic, CT), Dale Drum, George Brophy, The Hartford Courant, John Stewart, Marci Grzybowski, Mike Taylor, Paul Tyndall, Sandy Maniscalo, Shirley Courtois, testimonial ads, Travis Turner.
  - Notes, photographs, 1988; 1.4 Linear feet As received (Box 2012.0071_8)
    Subjects include: Ana Ramirez, Bryon French, Elizabeth Page, Mary Lou Reiner, Nancy Costello, Narda Gruver.
  - Fliers, notes, photographs, Early 1980s; 1.4 Linear feet As received (Box 2012.0071_9)
    Subjects include: unknown Bachelor of General Studies graduation commencement photographs used in brochure.
  - Correspondence, fliers, notes, photographs, 1998; 1.4 Linear feet As received (Box 2012.0071_10)
    Subjects include: commencement photographs taken by Peter Glass.
  - Correspondence, notes, optical disks, photographs, 2001-2002; 1.4 Linear feet As received (Box 2012.0071_11)
    Subjects include: commencement photographs taken by Peter Glass, Peter Glass Photography.
  - Administrative records, fliers, magnetic disk, optical disks, photographs, 2000-2001; 1.4 Linear feet As received (Box 2012.0071_12)
    Subjects include: Brigette Baynes, Denise Brown, Richard Gabehart, testimonial ads.
  - Optical disks, photographs, 2001; 1.4 Linear feet As received (Box 2012.0071_13)
    Subjects include: testimonial ads, Wendi Richardson.
  - Administrative records, fliers, photographs, publications, 1993-1994, 1997; 1.4 Linear feet As received (Box 2012.0071_14)
    Subjects include: Chandler Howard, Cheryl Michaud, Newsweek, testimonial ads, Time, U.S. News.
  - Administrative records, clippings, correspondence, notes, optical disks, photographs, 2004-2005; 1.4 Linear feet As received (Box 2012.0071_15)
    Subjects include: Elizabeth Williams, The Hartford Courant, Iris D'Oleo-Edwin, Murray Williams, The Register Citizen, Sherman McGrew, testimonial ads.
  - Administrative records, correspondence, fliers, notes, optical disks, photographs, 2003; 1.4 Linear feet As received (Box 2012.0071_16)
    Subjects include: Mariamarta Ariedondo, Marta Garrett, Mary Gates, Paul Blackman, testimonial ads.